

# TRÂN THỦY TRANG

### CONTACT

**2** 0907 24 79 71

tiffanytranthuytrang@gmail.com

26 Pham Van Hai, Tan Binh District

### **EDUCATION**

Ho Chi Minh University of Medicine & Pharmacy

Major: Pharmacy

# **ACTIVITIES**

A member of project team to organize some activities and events at IPSEN & Church.

# **HONOR & AWARD**

- 2014 Good sales Rep in GSK Exclusive.
- 2016 Best Effort Sale Rep in Tedis
- 2017 Best Sales Reps in HCM

#### **SKILLS**

- Handle objection & negotiation skills.
- Excellence communication.

# **CERTIFICATION**

- Certificate for Achievement:
   "Effective Communication Skills"
   from Dale Carnegie School of
   Business with highest performance.
- Certificate for complete: "Negotiation & Handle Objection Skills" from Robenny - School of Business.

# **ABOUT ME**

With more 5 years' experience as Medical Representative position at multinational companies, I possess aggressive thinking and good negotiating skills. My communication skills and positive attitude makes me an effective communicator with everyone; enthusiasm, integrity, good mind-set, hardworking and confident.

In more 2 years, I want to become a District Sales Manager.

# **EXPERIENCE**

IPSEN Pharma Viet Nam - Medical Representative/July 2017 - July 2018

- Regularly visit pharmacist to remind them on product. Develop & maintains good customer relationship, develop new customer & detailing product.
- Consult to the pharmacist about company products' advantages in order pharmacist understands clearly and deeply about product.
- Support my manager to lead our team and work closely with Intertal/External department. Support the company to implement the marketing strategy, coference or new product lauch event...
- Collect the production information from market as well as pharmacits's comments on products to report periodically to manager.
- As a member of Project Team, I support to organize NCM.
- Understanding and update the status of directly competitive.
- Achieved highest perfromance: 119% Q3'2017; 114% Q4'2017, 137% - Q1'2018 and 109% - Q2'2018.

**TEDIS Representative** – Medical Representative/Aug 2015 – Jun 2017

- Build customer relationship & detailing product. Build up marketing plan for each customer.
- Build strong team and lead the MR team to achieve objective.
- Ensure the sales targets implementation in territory; be responsible in these channels: Beauty store (Nuty, Beauty Hub, Epomi, ...)/
  Pharmacy Chain Pharmacy and Retailer.
- Understanding and update the status of directly competitive.
- Achieved 160% in 2016; 130% in Q1&Q2'2017; increase 30 % in the number of customer for each year.

**GSK Exclusive Team –** Medical Representative/Apr 2013 – Aug 2015

- Building strong customer relationship & detailing product.
- Support MKT team to organize symposium, Group discussion at pharmacy.
- Support Area sale Manager to lead our team. Certificate "Best Sales Rep" in 2014.
- Speak for Group Discussion as a Speaker member team.
- Management skills.
- Soft skill and office skills: Word, Excel, Powerpoint.

